This Christmas, love is just around the corner.
Fir Crazy is a comedy, romance, tv movie film directed by Craig Pryce.
When marketing executive Elise MacKenzie decides to help sell Christmas trees at her
family’s Christmas tree lot, she discovers a newfound fondness for the holidays.
But all could be lost when the store owner who hosts the tree lot on his block wants to shut
it down, and it’s up to Elise to find a way to rekindle his Christmas Cheer.
Elise, played by Sarah Lancaster.
Darren, played by Eric Johnson.
Gary, played by Colin Mochrie.
Shane, played by Gregory Ambrose Calderone.
Nanci, played by Inga Cadranel.
Betty, played by Lynne Griffin.
Riele Downs (born July 8, 2001) is a Canadian actress.
She began her career as a child actress, playing Faith
in the 2013 film The Best Man Holiday.
She went on to co-star as Charlotte on the Nickelodeon
television series Henry Danger from 2014 to 2020.
The film explores themes of christmas tree, christmas, fresh start.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.